字幕组
ZiMuZu.tv
原创翻译  双语字幕
最快首发美剧日剧下载请登录
字幕组网站www.ZiMuZu.tv
翻译：王大可 HOLA 小暴徒 木浅薰 Timothy
翻译：dzysteven 某羽   校对：油炸电风扇   木浅薰
时间轴：壬虚浪影  今  姜姜
后期：斯人      总监：某羽
诉 讼 双 雄
第六季   第五集
《诉讼双雄》前情提要
Previously on "Suits"...
我刚听说你拒绝了一位
I just heard you turned down a client
旗下投资机构价值二十亿美元的客户
whose investment firm is worth $2 billion.
我才不在乎它们价值多少
Well, I don't give a shit how much they're worth.
我是不会为威廉・萨特辩护的
I'm not representing William Sutter.
我没杀人
I didn't kill anyone.
这句话我说了十二年了
I've been saying it for 12 years,
而且我也可以证明
and I can prove it.
你到底要不要给彼此一个机会
Do you want to take a chance on each other or not?
肖恩・卡荷尔刚刚来找了我
I just got a visit from Sean Cahill.
他有办法把你弄出来
It turns out there's a way he can get you out.
条件是什么
What's the catch?
他需要你举报你的狱友
He needs you to inform on your cellmate.
-跟我说实话吧  -他拒绝了
- Tell me the truth. - He said no.
但是肖恩  我跟你说  他会回心转意的
But Sean, I'm telling you, he'll come around.
你知道为了让这件事开始进行
Do you know how many strings I pulled
我找了多少关系吗
to put this thing in motion?
你要履行承诺  把我弄出狱
You're gonna get me out of here like you promised.
-我从没保证过  -六周  哥们
- I never promised-- - Six weeks, brother,
我要是发现你在搞我
and if I find out you're screwing me,
你最好在监狱里的某个黑暗角落打个洞
you better hole up in some dark corner of this prison.
你愿意整修我在汉普顿的
How would you feel about renovating my summer house
-避暑别墅吗  -你确定吗
in the Hamptons? - Are you sure?
我这辈子从来没有这么确定过
I've never been as sure of anything in my entire life.
你一直都想把他带到这儿来
The whole time, you were always gonna bring him here.
因为这是完成任务的办法
Because this is the way to get it done.
那你为什么一开始不告诉我
Then why didn't you tell me that in the first place?
因为那结果会变成你想要利用瑞秋
Because it would've ended up with you wanting to use Rachel.
无论如何结果都是这样了  现在给我让开
It ended there anyway. Now get the hell out of my way.
哈维
Harvey!
我把一切都告诉瑞秋了
I told Rachel everything.
我接受协议
I'm taking the deal.
下面我们来研究一下你具体需要什么
All right, let's talk specifically about what you need.
我需要的是定罪
What I need is a conviction.
那当然  但从我这里来看需要什么
Obviously, but what exactly does that look like from my side?
就是一个铁证
It looks like a smoking gun,
因为我已经追查萨特三年了
'cause I've been after Sutter for three years now.
这个狡猾的混蛋
This guy's one slippery son of a bitch.
等等  威廉・萨特吗
Wait a second. William Sutter?
你在跟我开玩笑吗
Are you kidding me?
哈维  怎么了
Harvey, what's going on?
他上周来找过我让我为他辩护  但我拒绝了
He came to me a week ago to take him on, and I said no.
这件事你倒是做得很对
Well, it's a good thing you did.
-不  并没有  -你什么意思
- No, it isn't. - What are you talking about?
当凯文发现我拒绝了他的岳父
When Kevin finds out I told his father-in-law
他就再也不会相信迈克了
to drop dead, he's never gonna trust Mike.
如果你这话是我想的那个意思
If you're saying what I think you're saying,
你不能做他的律师
you're not taking this man as your client.
我就要做  因为如果我拒绝
Yes, I am, because if I don't,
也许这件事根本就做不了
we might as well not even be doing this.
-那就别做了  -看看我们现在的境况  肖恩
- Then let's not do it. - Look where we are, Sean.
我们正准备把迈克藏在车里带回监狱
We're in a car, sneaking Mike into prison.
你也动用了所有的关系
You pulled every string you have to make this happen.
你现在说要放弃
You're gonna pull out now?
是的  因为我不会让自己陷入
I am, 'cause I'm not gonna put myself
与你串通的境地
in position to collude with you.
我不会让你陷入那种境地的
I won't put you in that position.
我现在就在这种境地
I'm in that position right now.
你没有
No, you're not.
他现在还没有同意为任何人辩护
He isn't even representing anybody yet.
这次谈话完全是假设性的
This conversation is completely hypothetical.
我不需要罪犯的法律建议
I don't need legal advice from the convict,
我也不想因为你蓄意输掉官司
and I don't need to lose my career
而赔上自己的事业
because you tanked this guy's defense.
我没有蓄意做任何事
I'm not tanking anything.
我会为他竭尽全力
I'm gonna kick ass for him up and down the block,
也没有法律阻止我在此同时
and there's no law against me rooting for Mike
帮助迈克
while I'm doing that.
好吧  但你一旦做了任何威胁到我的事
Okay, but you cross one line that puts me in jeopardy,
我就会把这件事叫停
I'm gonna pull the plug on this whole thing.
那迈克在此之前最好找到
Well, Mike better get us what we need
我们需要的信息
before I have to do that.
你好
Hello?
瑞秋  我是邓巴教授
Rachel. Professor Dunbar.
-有什么事吗  -我知道你对
- What is it? - I know how passionate
伦纳德・贝利的案子充满热情
you were about Leonard Bailey,
但我刚收到无罪计划的反馈
but I just heard back from the Innocence Project,
他的案子不符合要求
and...I'm afraid his case doesn't qualify.
什么叫不符合要求
What do you mean it doesn't qualify?
我们有三个不同的证据用于上诉
We have three different grounds for an appeal.
但不幸的是  没有一种
And, unfortunately, none of them revolve
包含之前未被发现的DNA信息
around the existence of previously undiscovered DNA.
这有什么关系呢
What does that have to do with it?
他是被冤枉的
The man was railroaded.
他的案子应该被重审
He deserves to have his case retried.
关系非常大
It has everything to do with it,
因为在这样的案件中
because in a case like this,
这是是否符合要求的
that's the primary determinant
首要条件
for whether it qualifies or not.
我不在乎这符不符合要求
I don't care whether it qualifies or not.
我答应过伦纳德・贝利我会为他争取
I promised Leonard Bailey that I'd fight for him.
那你不应该那样做
Well, you shouldn't have done that.
教授  我知道我们不该
Professor, I know that we're not supposed
对我们的客户投入太多感情
to become emotionally invested in our clients,
但如果我们没有任何激情
but if we don't have any passion,
那我们最开始
then what's the point
为什么要帮他呢
of trying to help them in the first place?
瑞秋  我知道这件事听起来很难接受
Rachel, I understand this is a difficult thing to hear,
但我也无能为力
but there's nothing I can do.
我答应你
Look, I give you my word.
会给你找到一个新案子
We'll find you a new case.
-迈克  是你吗  -是我
- Mike, is that you? - Yeah, yeah.
睡觉吧  明早再聊
Go back to sleep. I'll talk to you in the morning.
你怎么样  还好吗
How are you? You all right?
还好
Yeah, I'm fine.
-怎么回事  -不管怎么回事
- What was it? - Whatever it was,
他们都没有查出来
they can't find a trace of it.
正式说法就是食物中毒
Officially, it's food poisoning.
我终于见到你的兄弟哈维了
Well, I finally got the chance to meet your buddy Harvey.
-哈维来了  -就在这里
- Harvey was here? - Mm-hmm, in this very cell.
-你跟我开玩笑吗  -骗你是小狗
- You're kidding me. - I shit you not.
你要是能见到就好了
You should've seen him.
我以为他要打加洛呢
Thought he was gonna attack Gallo right then and there.
-怎么没打  -警卫拦住了
- What stopped him? - Guards.
你确定没事吗
You sure you're okay?
没事
Yeah.
就是需要睡一觉
I just need to get some sleep.
很高兴你能回来  伙计
Well, it's good to have you back, buddy.
一旦你习惯身边有个能信任的人
Once you get used to having someone around you can trust,
就受不了自己独处了
it's hard to go back.
不管你在做什么  我希望你停下
Whatever it is you're doing, I want you to drop it
然后帮我在汉普顿买个别墅
and help me buy a house in the Hamptons.
-你说什么  -我说我需要在汉普顿
- Excuse me? - I said I need a large,
买一栋又大又贵的房子  最好靠近水边
expensive home in the Hamptons, preferably on the water.
路易  我不是有意要做你的商务经理
Louis, I don't mean to be your business manager,
但你为什么要在律所刚刚正要
but why are you buying a vacation home
回到正轨的时候买一栋度假住宅呢
when the firm's just getting back on its feet?
因为我告诉塔拉・梅瑟我在那里有一处房产
Because I told Tara Messer that I have a property out there,
而且我雇了她来重新装修
and I hired her to remodel it for me.
好的  让我先整理一下状况
Okay, let me get this straight.
你想花一大笔钱买一栋住宅
You want to spend a fortune buying a home
这样你就可以再花一大笔钱来重新装修吗
so that you can spend another fortune remodeling it?
这是能让我和她共处的唯一合理的方式
It's the only logical way that I can spend time with her.
-是吗  -是的
- Is it? - Yes.
还能有什么其他办法
What other way could there possibly be?
你可以直接约她出去
You could just ask her out.
-我才不要那么做  -为什么
- Well, I'm not gonna do that. - Why not?
-因为我不要  -路易
- Because I'm not. - Louis.
上帝啊  你为什么想要
Jesus Christ, why are you trying
-破坏我的感情生活  -你没有感情生活
- to sabotage my relationship? - You have no relationship.
这就是我想跟你说的
That's what I'm trying to tell you.
我没有感情生活
I have no relationship.
我孤身一人
I'm all alone.
自从希拉拒绝了我之后
Ever since Sheila rejected me,
我从未想过还能再找到真爱
I never thought I would find love again,
但这种感觉  我不知道
but there is something-- I don't know.
这个女人给我不同寻常的感觉
There's just something about this woman.
我觉得这次可能是我最后的机会了
I feel like this may be my last shot.
我明白  路易  而且如果你约她出去
I get that, Louis, and if you ask her out,
她会见到一位体贴
she is going to see a kind,
睿智的  任何女人
intelligent man that any woman
和他在一起都无比幸运的优秀男士
would be lucky to be in a relationship with.
但如果你这样做的话  当她发现真相之时
But if you do it this way, and she finds out,
你就会失去那最后的机会
then you lose that shot,
因为她再也不会相信你了
because she's never gonna trust you again.
看着我  唐娜
Look at me, Donna.
那样的一个女人
A woman like that...
拜托
Please.
我得先让她了解我
I need her to get to know me first.
好吧  路易
All right, Louis.
我会帮你找栋房子的
I'll help you find a house.
又在看我的照片吗
Looking at my pictures again?
-抱歉  -怎么了
- Sorry. - What's going on?
没什么  我只是
Nothing. I was just...
我只是在想  当时我问你
I was just thinking about when I asked you
是因为什么事情进来的时候  被人打断了
what you were in for. We got interrupted.
你从未告诉我答案
You never told me.
这样挺好
Oh, well, just as well,
因为我不想谈论这事
'cause I don't want to talk about it.
-好吧  为什么不呢  -为什么
- Okay, why not? - Why not?
因为如果我想说
'Cause if I wanted to talk about it,
我会说的
I'd be talking about it.
我明白我们
Look, I understand that we're not
不应该讨论这些事情的
supposed to talk about that stuff,
但是当你觉得你可能被某人下毒的时候
but when you think you might've been poisoned by somebody,
你就会想多了解一点
it makes you want to know something about the guy
和你共处一室的狱友
you're sharing a cell with.
你是想说你不信任我吗  迈克
You saying you don't trust me, Mike?
凯文  我是认真的
Kevin, I'm serious.
我跟你说了关于我自己的一切
I've told you pretty much everything about me,
而除了你不想让你的孩子来探视这个事实以外
and besides the fact that you don't want your kids to visit,
我对你一无所知
I don't know anything about you.
迈克  有很多事情
Look, Mike, there's a lot of things
我都可以告诉你
that I'm ready to tell you.
我只是还没准备好和你说那件事
I'm just not ready to tell you that.
好吗
Okay?
斯佩克特先生  你没有预约
Mr. Specter, you don't have an appointment.
没事的  朱莉
It's okay, Julie.
有人当着我的面叫我一坨屎
Someone calls me a piece of shit to my face,
我想知道返场小段会是什么
I want to know what the encore is.
你是过来往我地板上撒尿的吗
You here to piss on my floor?
我是过来告诉你  我最终决定接你的案子了
I'm here to tell you that I'm taking your case after all.
你怎么知道我没有在被你拒绝之后
Who says I didn't hire someone else
立马就雇佣了别人呢
the second you turned me down?
因为你不是从通讯录里找到的我
I do, because you didn't pick my name out of a phone book.
你来找我是因为你发现
You came to me because you found out
你的人在监狱里和我的人在一起
that your guy's in prison with my guy.
-如果就是如此呢  -别废话了  威廉
- So what if I did? - Cut the shit, William.
你女婿从我送进监狱的一位犯人手里救了迈克
Your son-in-law saved Mike from a guy I put behind bars.
那意味着我欠了你的情  你之前不跟我说
That means I owe you, and you didn't tell me about it
是因为你知道我会发现的
because you knew I'd find out
然后就会自己爬回来找你
and come crawling back on my own.
你没有爬啊
You're hardly crawling.
我小时候就没爬过
I didn't as a baby,
现在也不会
and I'm not gonna start now.
我只能做到这一步了
This is the best you're gonna get.
到底要不要合作
So are we doing this thing together or not?
好吧  你说服我了  哈维
Okay. You got me, Harvey.
现在怎么办
Now what?
现在我要去见你女婿
Now I go see your son-in-law.
为什么去见他
Why the hell would you want to do that?
因为他在坐牢  而你面临着公诉
Because he's in prison, and you're facing an indictment,
这让他成为了你最大的弱点
which makes him the biggest vulnerability you have.
丹伯里联邦监狱有人向你致电
You have a call from Danbury Federal Prison.
你愿意承担费用吗
Do you accept the charges?
愿意
Yes.
哈维  我们有麻烦了
Harvey, we have a problem.
-什么麻烦  -我试图和凯文谈谈
- What is it? - I tried to talk to Kevin.
什么也没问出来
I got nothing.
你想让我怎么做
Well, what do you want me to do about it?
我不知道  如果我有除了
I don't know. It would help
"你到底因为什么事进来的"
if I had something to talk about other than,
以外的话可以说  那应该会有所帮助
"Hey, what exactly are you in here for?"
好吧  迈克  你想要点话题吗
Okay, Mike, you want something to talk about?
我来给你找点话题
I'll get you something to talk about.
这不是我的白马公主嘛
Well, if it isn't my knight in beautiful armor.
你好吗  贝利先生
How are you, Mr. Bailey?
请叫我伦纳德
Please, call me Leonard.
恐怕有坏消息  伦纳德
I'm afraid I have some bad news, Leonard.
无罪计划审阅了那些新的证据  然后
The Innocence Project looked over the new evidence, and...
他们决定不接你这个案子
they decided not to take your case.
什么意思
What does that mean?
意思就是我无能为力了
It means there's nothing else I can do.
我就知道你根本帮不上我
I knew you couldn't do shit for me.
不  不  不  你不明白
No, no, no. You don't understand.
他们几乎从不接没有新DNA证据的案子的
They almost never take cases without new DNA evidence,
而你的案子没有这种证据
and yours had none.
我不在乎这一点
I don't care about that.
你请求我给你个机会冒险一试
You asked me to take a chance on you,
而现在你却过来告诉我你要放弃吗
and now you march in here and tell me you're giving up?
不  不  贝利先生
No, no, Mr. Bailey--
你说你会为我而战的
You said you would fight for me.
我确实努力过了
I did fight for you.
那就他妈的再努力一点
Well, then fight goddamn harder!
我很抱歉
I'm sorry,
我明白你的感受
and I understand how you feel,
但我真的无能为力了
but there's just nothing more that I can do.
你怎么能知道我的感受
How do you know what I feel?
你不知道与你爱的人
You don't know what it's like to be kept away
不能见面是什么滋味
from your loved ones.
-其实  我知道  -怎么回事
- Actually, I do. - How's that?
我的未婚夫也在监狱里
My fiancé's in prison.
刑期多久
How long?
-两年  -两年根本不算什么
- Two years. - Two years is nothing.
可这对我的影响却很大
It doesn't feel like nothing to me.
如果是终身监禁呢  瑞秋
What if it was forever, Rachel?
你会像放弃我一样放弃他吗
Would you give up on him like you did me?
我没有放弃你
I didn't give up on you.
你之前说你已经找到了有力证据
You said you found compelling evidence.
我也说过那点证据根本不够充分
I also said that it wasn't enough.
这话在我听来  就是放弃
That sounds like giving up to me.
哈维  你怎么来了
Harvey, what are you doing here?
我是来给你下正式通知的
I'm here to give you official notice.
现在我已经是威廉・萨特的律师了
I'm now William Sutter's attorney.
恭喜  希望你清楚自己该做些什么
Congratulations. I hope you know what you're doing.
我清楚  因为我此行就是来告诉你
I do, because I'm also here to notify you that
除非你在接下来的四十八小时内提起公诉
unless you bring an indictment in the next 48 hours,
我会起诉你和证监会对我客户造成了骚扰
I'm gonna sue you and the SEC for harassing my client.
你这话什么意思
What the hell are you talking about?
你听到了  你一直在
You heard me. You've been digging
调查他的账户  刺探他的员工
into his accounts, hounding his employees,
并且还审问他的出资人
and questioning his investors.
他因内线交易正在接受调查
He's under investigation for insider trading.
那些都是例行公事
That's how it works.
那样的话  提起公诉吧
Well, if that's how it works, then bring on an indictment.
我明白你的意图了
Ah, I see what you're doing.
我不采取点行动  迈克就撬不开凯文的嘴
Mike can't get Kevin to talk without me bringing an action.
我不知道你这话什么意思
I have no idea what you're talking about.
那也没关系
Oh, well, it doesn't matter, 'cause I'm not
因为在没有胜诉把握的情况下
bringing an indictment without knowing
我是不会提起公诉的
that I can win at trial.
可如果你连投石问路都不敢
And you're never gonna win at trial
就永远不会胜诉的
if you don't shake the trees and see what falls.
可恶  哈维  我不会在这个案子上和你串通
Damn it, Harvey, I am not colluding on this,
你居然来这里
and you're in here trying to get me
怂恿我对你自己的客户提起公诉
to bring an indictment against your own client.
因为你提起公诉后
Because when you bring that indictment,
我会打赢官司  可你不起诉
I'm gonna beat it, and if you don't bring it
且继续调查我的客户
and continue investigating my client,
我就会去告你
I'm gonna sue you, which is exactly
不管我的客户是谁  我都会那么做
what I'd be doing no matter who he was.
哈维  你想让我有所行动
You know what, Harvey? You want me to bring an action?
我就给你个行动
You got one.
天啊  原来你在这
Jesus Christ, there you are.
房子找得怎么样了
What's going on with the house hunt?
一切都在我的掌控中  路易
I am on top of it, Louis.
可我没看出来
Well, it doesn't look like you're on top of it.
我只看到你在这喝咖啡
It looks like you're drinking a goddamn cup of coffee.
我喝咖啡也许是因为昨晚通宵上网
Maybe that's because I was on the Internet all night
替你找房子  因为我很清楚
trying to find houses for you because I knew
你要求那么苛刻  肯定什么都看不上
that nothing would ever meet your insane specifications.
-是真的吗  -当然不是
- Is that true? - Not one word.
该死  唐娜  这很重要
Goddamn it, Donna, this is important.
眼下满大街都是
Right now there are hundreds of men out there
有海滨别墅的男人
with beach houses,
塔拉没准现在就在跟其中某个人约会呢
and Tara could be meeting any one of them.
多希望我此刻也在约会那种富豪
Right now I wish I was meeting any one of them.
唐娜  我以为你明白这不是玩笑
Donna, I thought you understood this isn't a joke.
我知道不是玩笑  路易
I know it isn't, Louis,
所以到现在我还没把找到的资料给你看
and that's why I haven't sent you anything I've seen so far,
因为我还没找到最合适的房子
because I haven't found the right thing yet.
我怎么感觉我不再相信你能够
And what if I said I lost confidence in your ability
时时刻刻都理解我的意图了呢
to know what I'm looking for in any given situation?
那我只好告诉你
Then I would say that that is exactly
这正是我一直都在躲着你的原因
why I've been avoiding you,
如果你还有点自知之明的话
and if you had any self-awareness at all,
就不会再来烦我  而是该信任我
you would stop bothering me and instead trust me for once.
你我都清楚这是永远不可能的
Well, we both know that's never gonna happen.
那你就自己去找房子吧  路易
Well, then, why don't you go find your own house, Louis?
-金[纸牌游戏]  -又赢了
- Gin. - Again?
跟你说了多少次了
How many times do I have to tell you?
不要跟过目不忘的人玩牌
Don't play cards with a guy with a photographic memory.
我也说过很多次  我肯定会赢你的
How many times I have to tell you I'm still gonna beat you?
发牌吧
Deal.
抱歉打扰你们钓鱼了
Sorry to interrupt your Go Fish.
有个叫哈维・斯佩克特要见你
There's a Harvey Specter here to see you.
算你运气好
Saved by the bell.
不是见你  罗斯  米勒
Not you, Ross. Miller.
能否告诉我为什么你要见我而不是迈克
Mind if I ask why you're here to see me instead of Mike?
因为我知道他还好
Because I heard he's okay,
并且我也不止是迈克的律师了
and I'm not just Mike's attorney anymore.
也是你的律师
I'm yours.
加洛的事不用你替我操心
I don't need your help with Gallo.
我说的不是加洛
I'm not talking about Gallo.
威廉・萨特找我来当他的代理人
William Sutter came to me to represent him.
我当时拒绝了他  后来却发现他的女婿
I turned him down until I found out that his son-in-law
一直在监狱里关照迈克
is the one who's been watching Mike's back.
谢谢你能这么说
Well, I appreciate that,
但这跟我又有什么关系
but what does that have to do with me?
我一般不会给我不信任的人当代理人
I don't make it a habit of representing people I can't trust.
你的意思是你不信任我
You saying you can't trust me?
我的意思是证监会认为威廉的公司
I'm saying the SEC thinks William's firm,
也就是你曾供职的公司
the one that you worked for,
犯了法
is breaking the law.
所以我想知道
So I need to know right now,
如果他们来找你  你会怎么说
when they come at you, what are you gonna say?
我会把上次对他们说的话
I'm gonna say the same thing I did
一字不差地再说一次
when they came at me the last time.
我岳父是清白的
My father-in-law's innocent.
这可以吗  我能走了吗
Is that it or can I go?
还有件事  凯文
One more thing, Kevin.
公诉方随时都会提起公诉
An indictment's coming down any second,
一旦那样
and once it does,
你就会成为所有狱友的出狱卡
that makes you every single inmate's ticket out of here.
因此  假如你对威廉的清白心存疑虑
So if you ever have a doubt about William's innocence,
就把它烂在肚子里
keep it to your goddamn self.
凯文  聊两句
Kevin, talk to you for a second?
怎么了  乔治
Yeah, sure. What's going on, George?
-是你室友的事  -他怎么了
- It's about your roommate. - What about him?
你还有心思在这玩牌
You got some nerve playing cards here
我的生命正在一分一秒地消逝
while my life is wasting away.
你想说什么
What are you talking about?
我的意思是
I'm talking about that motion
你不是说好了帮我递交动议吗
you were supposed to file for me.
你还是打听明白再来找我吧
Then you better get your facts straight,
我已经递交了
because I did file it.
没错  可被驳了回来
Yeah, and it got bounced right back.
-什么  不可能  -什么不可能
- What? No, that's not possible. - It is possible.
你在医务室美美地睡着
While you were taking your little siesta in the infirmary,
我却收到邮件说
I got an email that said
这玩意递交得都不对
the damn thing wasn't even filed right.
该死
Oh, goddamn it.
看来你没法信守承诺了
Looks like you can't keep your promises.
不  我能
No, I can keep it.
只是程序上出了问题
This is just some procedural mix-up, all right?
但我需要你的电话
But I'm gonna need to use your phone.
你逗我呢吧
Are you kidding me?
我说  我能解决这件事
I'm telling you that I can have this thing taken care of.
只是需要打个电话
I just need to make a phone call.
监狱里的电话有问题吗
What's wrong with the goddamn phones in here?
没有  但我今天已经用过了
Nothing, but I already used it today,
也就是说我得等两天后才能再用
which means I can't use it for another two days.
所以除非你想浪费这两天时间陪我打扑克
So unless you want to waste that time playing cards with me,
而且我保证你赢不了
which I guarantee you'll lose,
就赶紧把你的手机给我
you'll give me your phone right now.
我喜欢你  你很有种
I like you. You got balls.
我告诉你  我也一样
You know what? So do I,
所以我才能当着狱警的面
which is why I can take this out
拿出这玩意儿晃
in front of any guard in here
还知道我不会有麻烦
and know I'm not getting in any trouble.
给我记住了  赶紧把这事解决了
Don't forget that, and get that shit handled.
哈维  有东西给你
Harvey, I have something for you.
-什么东西  -来自肖恩・卡荷尔
- What is it? - It's from Sean Cahill,
需要你马上看
and I need you to take a look at it right away.
看什么啊  我知道诉状什么样
Why? I know what an indictment looks like.
不是诉状  哈维
It's not an indictment, Harvey.
他要吊销威廉・萨特的交易执照
He's suspending William Sutter's trading license.
给卡荷尔打电话
Get Cahill on the phone.
先生  哈维・斯佩克特的电话
Sir, I have Harvey Specter on the line.
你逗我呢吧
You've got to be shitting me.
哈维  有什么事吗
Harvey, what can I do for you?
你可以给我解释一下你要暂停我的
You can explain to me what the hell you're up to,
委托人的交易执照是想干什么
suspending my client's trading license.
你想让事情往下发展
You wanted to get the ball rolling.
这就是后续剧情
This gets the ball rolling.
这不是我想要的
This isn't what I wanted.
你也不是我老板
And I don't take orders from you.
上了庭我也没法阻止此事
And I'm not gonna be able to stop this in court,
那萨特肯定要解雇我
which means Sutter's gonna fire me.
那也许是你没理解我一开始的打算
Then maybe you didn't understand my initial position.
我才不在乎你会不会被解雇
I don't give a shit if you get fired or not.
你认为你需要代理萨特
You thought that you needed to represent Sutter,
所以你就做了你认为你该做的事
so you went ahead and did what you needed to do.
我认为我在有足够证据前
I thought I didn't want to bring an indictment
不想提起诉讼
before I had enough to win,
所以我就做了我认为该做的事
so I did what I needed to do,
但我现在该做的
but what I need to do right now
是吃完这个美味的火腿三明治
is finish this delicious ham sandwich,
意思就是说我希望下次我们谈话
which means the next time that I talk to you,
会是在法庭上
I expect it to be in court.
怎么回事
What's going on?
什么怎么回事
What do you mean, what's going on?
我们本来在玩牌
I mean, we're playing cards,
哈维来见你
and Harvey's here to see you,
接着我就发现你
and then next thing I know,
远远的对我死亡凝视
you're giving me some death stare,
然后就跑这儿来了
and you come out here.
什么事都没有
Nothing's going on.
哈维找你干什么
Well, what did Harvey want?
他要代理我岳父
He's representing my father-in-law,
所以他现在也是我的律师了
which means now he's also representing me.
满意了吗
That good enough for you?
好吧  凯文  你怎么这个态度
All right, Kevin, what's with the attitude?
-我是你这边的  -你是吗
- I'm on your side. - Are you?
因为哈维说我不该信任任何人
'Cause Harvey said I shouldn't trust anyone in here,
我认为  这应该包括你
and as far as I'm concerned, that includes you.
什么  这毫无道理
What? that doesn't make any sense.
你知道什么最没道理吗
You know what doesn't make any sense?
一分钟前  加洛还是你的敌人
One minute Gallo is your enemy,
一分钟后
and the next minute,
他就像你的好朋友一样把手机给你了
he's handing you his cell phone like he's your best friend.
我是在想办法把他弄出去
I'm trying to help him get out of here,
这样对我们都好
which is good for both of us.
你昨晚离开监狱也是去做这件事吗
Is that what you were doing last night outside of prison?
帮他出狱
You were helping him get out?
是这样吗
Is that what was going on?
凯文  好了
Kevin, come on.
我昨天还很担心你呢  室友
I was worried about you, cellmate.
我以为真的很严重
I thought you were in real trouble,
但他们不让我见你
but they wouldn't let me see you,
所以我托了一个
so I asked a friend of mine
在医务室工作的朋友去看你
who works in the infirmary to check on you,
十分钟前他告诉我  他十分确定
and ten minutes ago he told me that he's pretty damn sure
你至少离开了三个小时
you were gone for at least three hours.
你怎么解释
Well, what do you have to say about that?
我不在是因为去了医院
I was gone because I was in the hospital.
你怎么没告诉我
That's the first I'm hearing about it.
我告诉你干什么
Yeah, and why would I tell you that?
为什么不该告诉我
Why wouldn't you?
有什么事不对劲  我能看出来
Something's going on here, and I can tell.
好吧  凯文  你想知道真相
All right, Kevin. You want to know what happened?
真相就是哈维给了医生钱送我去医院
I went to the hospital because harvey paid the doctor
因为他不相信
because he didn't trust that
我能在监狱医务室活过昨晚
I would make it through the night in here,
而我没告诉你
and I didn't tell you
是因为我不想让你
because I didn't want to put you in a position
-替我说谎  -我告诉你
- where you'd have to lie for me. - You know what?
你这话听起来就是胡扯
That sounds like a whole lot of bullshit to me.
我告诉你  凯文
Yeah, you know what, Kevin?
我觉得最可笑的是你口口声声说你不信任我
I think it's pretty goddamn funny that you don't trust me
但你才是那个连进来的原因
when you're the one that won't even tell me
都不敢告诉我的人
what you're in here for.
不好  不好  不好
No. No. No.
该死  不好
Shit, no.
不好  不好  不好
No. No. No.
忙着呢  哈维
Not now, Harvey.
我正在处理重要的事
I'm in the middle of something important.
不管是什么  都没这个重要
Whatever it is, it's not as important as this.
这是什么
What is this?
暂停威廉・萨特交易执照的通知书
It's notice to suspend William Sutter's trading license.
问题是  怎么解决
The question is, what can be done about it?
没法解决
Nothing can be done about it.
什么叫没法解决
What do you mean, nothing can be done about it?
你不是财务大师吗
You're supposed to be the financial wizard.
我的确是  而且我明确告诉你
I am, and I'm telling you
这种东西是证交所出的
that this kind of thing is at the SEC's discretion.
他们有权力
They have unlimited power
暂停任意交易执照九十天
to suspend trading licenses up to 90 days.
-该死  -只有九十天
- Goddamn it. - It's only 90 days.
九十天我就被解雇了
90 days gets me fired.
没事的  哈维
Well, it's gonna be okay, Harvey.
我知道最近公司状况不太好
I mean, I know things have been rough around here,
但是已经有起色了
but business is picking up.
不是为了生意  路易
This isn't about business, Louis.
是为了迈克
It's about Mike.
你瞒着我什么  哈维
What are you not telling me, Harvey?
我不会告诉你细节
I'm not gonna tell you the details,
是因为不想让你也担风险
because I'm not gonna put you at risk,
但我有个机会让迈克早点出来
but I have a chance to get Mike out early,
要是没了这个动议  这事儿就黄了
and if I lose this motion, it's over.
我会想办法解决这件事的
Well, then I'll figure out a way to get it done.
谢谢你  路易
Thank you, Louis.
-我是哈维・斯佩克特  -哈维  是我
- This is Harvey Specter. - Harvey, it's me.
迈克  你哪里来的私人电话
Mike, what the hell are you doing with a private phone?
你代理凯文又是怎么回事
What the hell are you doing representing Kevin?
是你没办法让他说实话
You were the one having trouble getting him to open up.
然后你觉得告诉他不要相信这里的任何人
And you thought telling him not to trust anyone in here
就是解决办法吗
was the answer to that?
听着  我这么做是为了让他相信我
Look, I did that to get him to trust me,
因为他相信了我  就会相信你
because if he trusts me, he trusts you.
好吧  但有件事你没料到
Yeah, well, you didn't count on one thing.
他知道我昨晚晚没在医疗室
He knows I wasn't in the infirmary the whole night.
什么  他怎么知道的
What? How the hell does he know that?
他有个熟人在那里工作
Some guy he knows works there.
我骗他说你带我去了医院
I told him some story about you taking me to the hospital,
但他不相信
but he's not buying it.
那你就要想个办法让他相信
Then you figure out a way to make him buy it.
好  我会想办法的
Fine, I'll think of something,
但这不是我唯一的问题
but that's not my only problem.
又怎么了
What now?
加洛的动议被退回来了
Gallo's filing came back.
这个动议需要
It needs to be filed in person
由其辩护律师本人提出
and it needs to be filed by his attorney of record.
你逗我呢吧
You got to be shitting me.
你要我代理那个野兽
You want me to represent that animal?
如果你不这样做  那让凯文说实话
If you don't, then getting Kevin to talk
就只能算是个小问题了
is gonna be the least of my problems.
瑞秋  我需要你帮忙
Rachel, I need your help with something.
什么事
What can I do?
我要你给弗兰克・加洛起草一份保释申请文件
I need you to draft a parole application for Frank Gallo.
迈克不是正在办吗
I thought Mike was doing that.
出现了问题
There was a problem,
所以我还需要你起草一份任命书
which is also why i need you to draw up an engagement letter
让我代理弗兰克・加洛
for me to be Gallo's attorney.
行
Done.
你怎么了
What is it?
你听到了你之前跟路易发脾气
I heard you get upset with Louis earlier,
然后你又因为加洛的事情来找我
and now you're coming to me about Gallo.
所以我只是想知道你是否
So...I just need to know if you think
真的认为卡荷尔这整件事行得通
this whole Cahill thing's really gonna work.
瑞秋...
Rachel--
哈维  告诉我真相吧
Harvey, just tell me the truth.
听着  我不知道行不行得通
Look, I don't know if it's gonna work or not,
但是我知道我不会放弃
but I do know I'm not gonna stop trying.
不得不说  作为一个刚在院子
Got to say, you don't look so bad for a guy
晕倒的过人  你的气色还不错
who blacked out in the yard the other day.
是啊  他们照顾得好
Yeah, they took good care of me.
我很高兴你没事
Well, I'm glad you're okay.
有什么事
What's on your mind?
我要你为我给典狱长捎个口信
I need you to get a message to the warden for me.
当然可以
Sure.
我们例行每周早午餐的时候就告诉他
I'll bring it to him at our weekly brunch.
你要我传什么口信
What would you like for it to say?
-我认真的  -我才不管你怎样
- I'm serious. - I don't care what you are.
你想要给典狱长捎口信
You want to get a message to the warden,
你就要通过正当途径
you go through the proper channels
自己跟他说
and get it to him yourself.
我不能走正当程序
I can't go through the proper channels,
因为这事儿得保密
because nobody can know about it.
好吧  迈克  告诉我是什么情况
All right, Mike, tell me what's going on.
为了早出狱我做了交易
I made a deal to get out of here early.
什么样的交易
What kind of deal?
告发某个人之类的
The kind where I inform on someone.
谁
Someone?
凯文・米勒
Kevin Miller.
-迈克  不是吧  -朱利叶斯  容我解释
- Mike, come on. - Julius, let me explain.
我不需要你解释
I don't need you to explain.
你要背叛你的室友  之前还要我保护的那个
You are betraying your cellmate, who you came to me to protect.
不  我是要让那个罪行比我
No, what I am doing is putting away someone
更恶劣却仍逍遥法外的人进监狱
who is out there doing worse things than I ever did.
所以我不需要你的评判  我需要你的帮助
So I don't need your judgment. I need your help.
抱歉  我的工作不是为你做这些
I'm sorry, it's not my job to help you do something like this.
不  你的工作帮我做好出狱生活的准备
No, it's your job to help me prepare for life after prison.
而这个能让出狱生活
Well, this is gonna make life after prison
更快实现
come a hell of a lot faster.
好  你想这么做吗
Well, fine, you want to do this?
那你就去做吧  但我不会帮你的
You go ahead and do it, but I am not gonna be complicit.
你一直说让我相信你  冠冕堂皇
You know what? You talk a big goddamn game about trusting you,
但相信你到底意味着什么
but what does that trust mean?
现在  我要给典狱长捎个信
Now, I need to get to the warden,
我要在守卫不发现的情况下捎给他
and I need to do it without the guards finding out.
你到底帮不帮我
Can you help me or not?
瑞秋  这么晚你怎么来了
Rachel, what are you doing here so late?
教授  您有时间吗
Professor, do you have a minute?
当然  坐吧
Of course. Yeah, sit down.
我今早去看了伦纳德・贝利
I went to see Leonard Bailey this morning
告诉他我们放弃了他
to tell him we were turning our backs on him.
没有人放弃他  瑞秋
No one's turning their back on him, Rachel.
只是我们有了更好的案子
There are just better cases.
无意冒犯  但这是屁话
No offense, but that's bullshit.
-什么  -你也看了他的文件
- Excuse me? - You read his file.
里面有足够的证据能够让他重新受审
There's enough evidence in there for him to get a new trial,
可我们却要让他烂在死囚监狱里
and instead we're gonna let him rot on death row.
瑞秋  我知道你的感受
Rachel, I understand how you feel,
-但有些事情...  -我想我是
- but there are some things that-- - I feel like
弃了您的课才接手的这个案子
I dropped your class to take this case.
我也告诉你我可以再给你一个案子
And I told you I'd get you another one.
我不想要其他的案子  我就想要这个
I don't want another one. I want this one.
瑞秋  我不能再
Rachel, I cannot provide you
提供资源来支持你了
with the resources and the backing anymore.
好  要是如果我自己能找到资源
Okay, so what if I were able to provide my own resources
并找到一位合格律师来监督我呢
and--and to get the supervision of a qualified lawyer?
你什么意思
What are you talking about?
我在皮-斯-利律所工作  教授
I work at Pearson Specter Litt, Professor.
大家都知道他们会时不时地
They've been known to take a pro bono case
接手一些公益案
from time to time.
好
Okay.
好  你赢了  瑞秋  但这是很不合规矩的
Okay, you win, Rachel, but this is highly irregular.
我不在乎
I don't care.
这也不是我们
That's not a good enough reason
放弃伦纳德・贝利的充分理由
to turn our backs on Leonard Bailey.
不要再质疑我高超的财务能力了
Well, don't ever question my financial wizardry again.
说说看
Let's have it.
我想破了脑袋
I was banging my head against the wall,
想要找到一个阻止吊销的办法
trying to figure out a way to stop the suspension,
然后我灵机一动
but then it dawned on me.
我们根本不需要阻止这件事
We don't need to stop it.
如果我们能让萨特的公司成为
If we can turn Sutter's firm into the subsidiary
一个独立控股公司的子公司
of a separate holding company,
我们就能让其他人来帮他运营
we can find someone else to execute the trades for him.
-漂亮  -是啊  但唯一的问题是
- Beautiful. - Yeah, but the only issue is,
我们需要找到些愿意
we need to find traders that are willing
资助那个混蛋的交易员
to bankroll the son of a bitch,
鉴于他的名声
given his reputation.
这不是什么问题
Well, that's not gonna be a problem.
不  哈维  这不是个小问题
No, Harvey, this is not nothing.
没人愿意和那家伙共事
Nobody wants to work with this guy.
你忘记在我们对面的朋友了
You're forgetting our new friends across the hall.
什  什么  你在逗我吗
What? What, are you kidding me?
你认为那个混蛋会答应我的要求吗
You think that asshole's gonna say yes to me?
没关系  我知道他会答应谁的要求
It's okay. I know who he'll say yes to.
哈维
Harvey,
我知道迈克走后你心里不好受
I know how tough it's been not having Mike here,
我只是想让你知道我也很想念他
and I just want to let you know that I miss him too.
我很感谢  路易  但你没有必要说这些
I appreciate that, Louis, but you didn't have to say it,
因为行动胜于言语
because actions speak louder than words,
你所做的这些已经说明了一切
and you doing this says it all.
哈维  我找了你一天了
Harvey, I've been looking for you all day.
你找到我了
Well, here I am.
或许你可以告诉我为什么
Then maybe you can tell me why all of a sudden
我们突然又代理威廉・萨特了
we're representing William Sutter.
-我改变主意了  -你改变主意了
- I changed my mind. - You changed your mind?
是你告诉我为萨特辩护就如同出卖灵魂
You told me taking Sutter on would be like selling your soul,
但是现在你突然180度大转弯
and now you're doing a complete 180.
杰西卡  我
Jessica, I--
不  哈维
No, Harvey,
我不是说我不高兴
I'm not saying I don't like it.
我只是想知道到底是为什么
I just want to know what's going on.
萨特是卡荷尔的目标
Sutter's the one Cahill's after.
你逗我呢吧
You've got to be kidding me.
绝对没有
I shit you not.
好吧  我懂了
well, I get it.
你为他全力辩护
You give him a full-throttle defense,
取得他的信任
gain his trust,
然后向上帝祈祷迈克能釜底抽薪
and hope to God Mike cuts his legs out.
正是这样
Exactly.
怎么了
What?
他会把他的投资业务交给我们打理吗
Is he gonna give us his investment business?
除非我们赢了这场官司
Not until after we win.
但我们又不能赢
Which we're hoping we don't.
-杰西卡  我必须要这样做  -哈维  别紧张
- Jessica, I have to do this. - Harvey, relax.
我同意  代理他能减少经济负担
I'm on board. It pays the bills,
我们还能利用它来找到更多的业务
and we can leverage it into more business anyway,
但我们最好尽快利用
but we'd better leverage it fast,
因为输掉这场官司对迈克也许是好事
because losing this case might be good for Mike,
但对我们来说不是
but it's not gonna be good for us,
我不知道你怎么想的
and I don't know about you,
但我想再次回到顶峰
but I'd like to get back on top.
这正是我所想的
There's nothing I'd like more,
也是我来这里的原因
which is why I came in here.
你需要什么
What do you need?
我需要你让那些交易员帮个忙
I need you to get something from those traders.
站起来  罗斯  你被单独监禁了
On your feet, Ross. You're going to solitary.
什么  等等  你什么意思
What? Wait, what are you talking about?
你听到我说的了  单独监禁24小时  走吧
You heard me. 24 hours, let's go.
不  我哪也不跟你去
No, I'm not going anywhere with you
除非你告诉我到底发生了什么
until you tell me what's going on.
我让你去哪你就去哪
You'll go where I tell you to,
否则你就等着尝尝这个的滋味
or you'll get acquainted with this.
听着  我只想知道为什么
Listen to me. I just want to know why--
再问问题  监禁时间就翻倍
Next question makes it 48 hours.
走不走
You coming or not?
你做了什么
What did you do?
杰西卡  太好了  我找到你了
Jessica--good, I caught you.
瑞秋  怎么了
Rachel, what is it?
你还记得无罪计划的案子吗
Do you remember my Innocence Project case?
我怎么能不记得呢  厉害的瑞秋
How could I not? Badass Rachel.
谢谢你  我接了那个案子
Well, thank you. So I took it,
但现在他们说那个案子不符合无罪计划
but now they're saying that it doesn't qualify.
让我猜猜
Let me guess.
你想让我们作为公益诉讼来接下那个案子
You want us to take it on as a pro bono.
我需要的仅仅是你每周花一个小时监督我
All I need is one hour a week of supervision,
如果我需要出庭  你得陪着我
and if I need to appear in court, you come with me.
我知道我要求很多  但是
I know that that's a lot to ask, but--
瑞秋  我希望我能告诉你我有额外的一小时给你
Rachel, I wish I could tell you I had an extra hour to give,
-但我没有  -杰西卡  拜托了
- but I don't. - Jessica, please.
如果你能跟我来见见这个男人
If you would just come with me and meet this man--
不  这正是我所说的
No, this is my point.
我才发现我们拥有的将律所扶上正轨的时间
I just found out we have less time than I thought we did
比我们想得更少
to get this firm back on its feet,
我负担不起花任何额外的时间在其他事情上
and I can't afford to spend one minute on anything else.
但  我真的
But, I mean, really--
瑞秋  我很抱歉
Rachel, I'm sorry.
失陪了
Now if you'll excuse me.
谢谢你
Thank you.
谢谢你的心理咨询师吧  罗先生
Thank your counselor, Mr. Rowe.
-我会的  -你一定很信任他
- I will. - You must trust him a lot
才敢让他知道你的打算
to let him in on your little arrangement.
我确实信任
I do.
他帮了我  虽然他不认同这件事
He helped me, even though he doesn't approve of this.
听起来你也不太认同
Sounds like you don't either.
这与我认同与否毫不相关
It's not up to me to approve or not.
你来这里就是为了告诉我这些
Is that what you came down here to tell me?
不  我来这里是想告诉你
No, I came down here to tell you I've been doing this
我做这行很久了
a long time,
我见过很多犯人来了又走
and I've seen a lot of inmates come and go.
这种交易  它们并不总是很顺利的
These kind of deals, they don't always work out so well.
你是说我会在这待上整整两年
You saying you think I'll be here for the whole two years?
我是说  我希望最终结果不会变得更糟
I'm saying I hope it doesn't turn out even worse than that.
不是已经休市了吗
I thought the markets were closed.
《华尔街:  金钱永不眠》
Did you ever see "Wall Street
看过吗
Money never sleeps"?
-这是什么  -看看就知道
- What's this? - Have a look.
让我把话说清楚  我雇了你
Let me get this straight. I hire you,
结果你做的第一件事就是来找我帮忙
and the first thing you do is come to me for a favor?
之前你是我的租客时  我来找你帮过忙
I came to you for a favor when you were my tenant.
现在作为你的律师  我是来给你一个商机
Now, as your lawyer, I am coming to you with an opportunity.
什么意思
What are you talking about?
这不是一个慈善捐赠
That's not a charitable donation.
你接了它  你会得到该有的报酬
You do this, you'll get paid for it.
-多少  -足够多
- How much? - Enough.
我怎么知道没有风险
How do I know I'm not leaving something on the table?
因为我做事从来把握十足
Because I never leave anything on the table.
好吧
All right.
我不明白
You know, I don't get it.
你明显是个顶尖的律师
You're obviously a big-time attorney,
现在你却转租给我
and now you're subletting to me.
这是怎么一回事
What the hell happened here?
-你不知道吗  -我为什么会知道
- You don't know? - Why would I?
-谷歌一下  -这么糟啊
- Google it. - That bad?
我们雇了个律师
We hired a lawyer.
后来发现他说了谎  这毁掉了我们的声誉
Turns out he was a fraud. It ruined our reputation.
发现他说谎  还是你一直都知道
Turned out to be a fraud, or you knew he was a fraud?
晚安  斯图  明天见
Good night, Stu. See you in the morning.
典狱长  你这是...干什么
Warden, what are you-- what are you doing?
你知道迈克・罗斯
Did you know Mike Ross
那天晚上离开了监狱吗
left the prison grounds the other night?
-什么  -别跟我打哈哈
- What? - Don't bullshit me.
你知道他的律师  就我所知现在也是你的律师
Did you know his lawyer, who I understand is now also your lawyer,
贿赂了某些人把他带出去了吗
paid someone to get him out of here?
我完全不知道这事
I don't know anything about it.
那我想如果我问你
I suppose if I asked you
他贿赂了谁  你也会是一样的答案了
who he paid, you'd have the same answer.
如果下次我发现你说谎
I find out you're lying, next time,
进单独监禁的就会是你了
you are gonna be the one in solitary,
而且绝不只是一晚
and it won't be just one night.
-什么  -我只是在想象
- What? - I'm just thinking about
当这个混蛋发现
when this asshole finds out
你要废掉他吊销执照那招时的表情
you're gonna blow his bullshit suspension out of the water.
威廉  我会废掉它的
William, I am gonna blow it out of the water,
但我需要你先签了这个
but I'm gonna need you to sign this first.
史蒂芬投资集团是什么东西
What the hell is Stevens Investment Group?
是你以后所有交易都要由其经手的公司的名字
It's the company you're trading through from now on.
胡闹  他们还成我的主人了
Bullshit. They own me?
他们谁的主人都不是
They don't own anything.
只是纸面上看起来控制着你
They control you on paper,
除非你接下来90天想继续停业
and unless you want to shut down for the next 90 days,
否则就得这么办
this is what you have to do.
胡说
Well, bullshit.
那家伙要告我  你要怎么办
What are you gonna do if that guy indicts me,
让我签认罪协议  然后缓刑吗
cut a deal where I plead guilty, and I get probation?
因为如果这就是你的赢局
'Cause if this is what you consider winning,
那我还是换个律师比较好
I might as well find myself another lawyer.
好了  先生们  我准备听听辩论了
Okay, gentlemen, I'm ready to hear arguments,
但我得告诉你们
but I have to tell you,
除非昨晚国会出台了新法律
unless Congress passed a new law last night,
否则停业不会取消
this suspension stands.
没关系  法官大人
That's okay, Your Honor.
我客户的公司
My client's firm is now
目前是一家上市公司的子公司
the subsidiary of a holding company
并不使用已被吊销的营业执照
with a different trading license.
-什么  -文件都在这里
- What? - It's all right here.
这样的话
In that case,
我动议暂时吊销那家公司的执照
I move to have that company's license suspended.
出于这个原因
And that, right there, is why I'd like to ask the court
我申请法庭
to have Mr. Cahill removed
裁定卡荷尔就未来
from any investigation
对我当事人的所有调查进行回避
regarding my client in the future.
你疯了吗
Are you out of your mind?
法官大人  我们曾经强烈敌对
We have an antagonistic history, Your Honor.
所有人都知道  而这次调查
Everyone knows it, and this action
无非是在找借口
is nothing more than a stunt
试图通过我的客户来惩罚我
designed to punish me through my client.
荒谬之极
This is ridiculous.
我已经调查威廉・萨特18个月了
I've been investigating William Sutter for 18 months.
而在这过去的18个月中
And in the last 18 months,
他什么行动都没有
he took no action,
而昨天  当我通知他
and then yesterday, when I informed him
我成为了萨特先生的律师后
I am Mr. Sutter's attorney,
不到5小时他就吊销了他的执照
within five hours he suspends his license,
现在他还想再来一次
and now he's trying to do it again.
这才叫赢局
That's what I call a win.
卡荷尔先生  这看起来可不太好
Mr. Cahill, this doesn't look good.
我倾向于要求你回避
I'm inclined to take you off this case.
法官大人  斯佩克特先生说得对
Your Honor, Mr. Specter is right.
我们是有过节  但我处理此案
We have history, but I've been involved
时间比他要长得多
in this case a lot longer than he has.
如果说有谁应为利益冲突回避
So if anyone has to be thrown out for a conflict,
那也是他  不是我
it is him, not me.
我哪也不去  法官大人
I'm not going anywhere, Your Honor.
那么就请萨特先生
Then let Mr. Sutter waive
声明放弃所有利益冲突权利
any claims to conflict altogether,
除非你想开个先例
unless, of course, you want to set a precedent
让所有不喜欢公诉人的被告
that any time a defendant doesn't like his prosecutor,
只要雇个以前跟公诉人
all he has to do is hire a lawyer
起过冲突的律师就能解决问题
he's gone up against before.
萨特先生  你想要继续雇佣你的律师
Mr. Sutter, would you like to keep your attorney
还是换一个呢
or hire another one,
因为我不会要求卡荷尔先生回避
because I am not taking Mr. Cahill off this case.
法官大人  我就选哈维
Harvey's my guy, Your Honor.
那没有其他问题的话
Then unless there's some other issue,
本次庭审到此结束
the court has a full docket.
狱警说有人来访
Guard tells you you have a visitor,
但不说是谁  会让人误以为
doesn't say who it is, you start thinking
是安吉丽娜・朱莉终于看了人家的信呢
maybe Angelina Jolie opened your letters after all.
坐吧  加洛
Sit down, Gallo.
你是来继续诬告我的吗
You here to make more false accusations?
我是来跟你说  从现在开始
I'm here to tell you that, as of this minute,
我是你的新律师
I'm your new attorney.
什么
Come again?
你需要有人帮你申请动议
You need someone to file that motion.
我就是那个人
I'm that someone.
要是我不想要你帮忙呢
What if I don't want your help?
那你就可以烂在这里等刑期结束了
Well, then you can rot in here for the rest of your sentence.
其实挺好笑的  不是吗
It's actually kind of funny, isn't it,
现在你努力地想要弄我出去
you fighting to get me out
而当初也是你花了那么大力气才把我弄进来
when you fought so hard to put me away.
这肯定让你痛不欲生
Must kill you.
我确实觉得很恶心
Makes me sick to my stomach,
但我会忍下去
but I'm gonna live with it,
因为你会给我回报的
because you're gonna give me something in return.
是吗  什么回报
Oh, yeah? What's that?
事情进行过程中
Until this thing goes through,
你不仅不能找迈克的麻烦
not only are you gonna keep your hands off Mike,
还要做他的私人保镖
you're gonna be his personal protector in here.
-胡说八道  -不是胡说
- Bullshit. - Not bullshit.
就算他放风的时候扭个脚
He so much as twists an ankle in the yard,
我也会撤回动议
I'll withdraw that motion.
你是不是忘了点什么  大人物
Now, aren't you forgetting a little something, champ?
我不需要你帮我做这件事
I don't need you to handle this thing for me.
我现在知道情况了  自己会找律师
Now that I know what's what, I'll get my own attorney.
你去找  我就跟法庭说
Yeah, you do that, and I'll tell the courts
你向我承认了曾试图给迈克下毒
that you just admitted to me that you tried to poison Mike.
你知道那会给你加多少年刑吗
You know how much time that's gonna add to your sentence?
-我什么都没做  -那真好
- I didn't do shit to him! - Good for you.
但你觉得他们会信谁
Who do you think they're gonna believe,
我这样的前任检察官
a former prosecutor like me
还是你这样被判刑的线人
or an informant convict like you?
当然  如果我是你的律师
Of course, if I'm your attorney,
我就什么都不能说了
I can't tell them any of that.
你这个混蛋
You son of a bitch.
你陷害我
You set me up.
一点没错
I sure as hell did.
所以决定权在你
So it's up to you.
你同意  还是不同意
You in or you out?
能跟你说句话吗
Can I talk to you a second?
什么事  路易
What is it, Louis?
我找不到房子
I can't find a house.
房子  什么房子
A house? What house?
我不知道什么房子的事
I don't know anything about a house,
特别是当这个房子
certainly not for a person
是为一个不相信我有能力在特定情况下
who doesn't have any confidence in my ability
知道他需求的人找的
to know what he's looking for in a given situation.
唐娜求你了  我们不能假装我什么都没说吗
Donna, please, can't we just pretend that I didn't say
就像我们一直以来那样
what I said, like we usually do?
不  路易  不行  因为我得确定
No, Louis, we can't, because I need to know
你至少花了点时间好好反省了
that you have spent at least one second contemplating
你那股无名火是从哪来的
what your little outburst was about.
我知道是从哪来的
I know what it was about.
是吗  哪来的
Really? What is that?
我想你了  唐娜
I miss you, Donna.
想念你做我秘书的一切
I miss having you as my secretary.
我也想你  路易
I miss you too, Louis.
但别误会
And don't get me wrong.
我没说格雷琴不好
I'm not saying Gretchen's not great.
谁这么说了啊
Who would?
我只是说...她不是你
It's just--I'm just saying she's not you.
-那谁是  -没人能是
- Who is? - Nobody.
这是你要找的东西吗
Was this the kind of thing you're looking for?
天呐  太完美了  还能下手吗
Oh, my God, it's perfect. Is it still available?
-今早有人开了价  -那我们得出个高点的
- An offer went in this morning. - We have to beat it.
不  路易  不用
No, Louis, we don't.
那个价是你开的
That offer was yours.
他们接受了吗
Did they take it?
明天就知道了
We find out tomorrow.
-唐娜  -不许
- Donna-- - No.
典狱长的事我很抱歉
I'm sorry about what happened with the warden.
哦
Yeah.
如果你有什么需要...
If you need anything--
我会跟你说
I'll let you know.
我没有  我没有告诉他们
Look, I didn't-- I didn't tell them
你跟我说的哈维带你出去的事
what you told me about Harvey getting you out.
我得让你知道  这对我很重要
I need you to know that. It's important to me.
好  随你怎么说吧  凯文
Yeah, whatever you say, Kevin.
我知道我没跟你说我为什么在这里  迈克
I know I haven't told you why I'm in here, Mike...
但你懂
But you don't understand.
我一进这里  就得注意
From the second I got here, I've had to watch
我说的话  每个字都得小心
what I say, every single word,
每天早上醒来
and every morning I get up,
我都提醒自己
and I remind myself
不要跟错误的人说错误的话
not to say the wrong thing to the wrong person,
没晚我上床时都会想
and every night I go to bed and think,
"终于又小心翼翼过完了一天"
"Another day down where I didn't."
你觉得我不懂这种感觉吗
Yeah, you think I don't know what that's like?
我在一个谎言里生活了好几年
I've been living a lie every day for years.
是  但你只是在保护你自己
Yeah, but you were just protecting yourself.
你没有家庭
You don't have a family.
凯文  你做了什么
Kevin, what did you do?
我跟妻子吵了一架
I got in a fight with my wife.
状况...
It was...
很糟糕
it was bad.
我们都对对方说了从未有过的过分的话
We said things to each other we never said before.
我离开了家
I went out.
喝醉了
I got drunk.
我开着车
I got into my car,
差点撞死人
and I almost killed someone.
之后我记得的  就是我在救护车上
Next thing I knew, I woke up in an ambulance,
面前坐着位警官
looking up at a police officer.
什么
What?
我犯了一个非常愚蠢的
I made one stupid,
非常愚蠢的错误
stupid mistake.
代价是我得离开家庭3年  而且我错过的
And it's gonna cost me three years with my family,
不光是他们生命中重要的时刻  朋友
and it's not just the special things, man.
我错过了上千次
I'm missing a thousand chances
早晨抱抱我的孩子的机会
to hug my kids in the morning...
晚上亲吻我妻子的机会
and kiss my wife good night,
只是因为我没有控制好自己
all because I couldn't control myself.
你跟你妻子是因为什么吵的架
What were you fighting with your wife about?
你说你在保护家庭  是什么意思
What do you mean, you were trying to protect your family?
凯文
Kevin.
我...不能说
I--yeah, I can't.
不能说
I just can't.
好
Okay.
我接受
I'll do it.
-你说什么  -你的法律援助案件
- Excuse me? - Your pro bono.
明早带文件来
Bring me the file tomorrow morning.
抱歉杰西卡  我能问问为什么吗
Jessica, I'm sorry. Can I just ask why?
原因重要吗
What does it matter?
对我重要
It matters to me.
我在外面忙了一天
I've been out all day,
尝试招揽客户  但很艰难
trying to drum up business, and it hasn't been easy.
所以从现在开始  人们搜索我们的名字时
So from now on, when people Google our name,
我更希望他们看到
I'd rather they see,
"皮尔逊-斯佩克特律所救下无辜之人"
"Innocent man freed by Pearson Specter"
而不是"曼哈顿律所雇佣诈骗犯"
than "Manhattan law firm hires a fraud."
谢谢你
Thank you.
晚安  瑞秋
Good night, Rachel.
肖恩  你来干什么
What are you doing here, Sean
你很清楚我来干什么
Oh, you know what I'm doing here.
你怎么想的  要法庭强迫我回避我的案子
What were you thinking, trying to get me thrown off my own case?
他在找我麻烦  我得做点事保证他的信任
He was coming at me. I had to do something to keep his trust.
那我告诉你
Well, for your information,
如果我被要求回避了
if I get thrown off this case,
那个你不知道的
that deal that you don't know about
让某人提前出来的协议  也就不存在了
getting that certain someone out early doesn't exist anymore.
你以为我不知道吗
You think I don't know that?
不  我觉得你不知道
No, I don't think you do,
因为如果不是我灵机一动
because if I hadn't pulled that shit out of my ass,
这件事已经黄了
this whole thing would've been for nothing.
你在高兴什么
What are you so pleased with yourself about?
没什么  只是...
Nothing. It's just...
你一开始就不想让我接这个案子
you didn't want me to take this case,
现在又因为我辩护太得力
and now you're getting pissed at me
而对我不满
because I'm too good a job defending my client.
你要这么说的话...
Now that you put it that way...
你的招接得很漂亮  肖恩
It was a good fix, Sean.
你的招出得也不错  哈维
It was a good move, Harvey.
想去喝一杯吗
Want to get a drink?
不如就在这儿喝怎么样
Why don't we just have one here?
最后一杯  恐怕我们很久都不能一起喝酒了
This might be the last one that we have together for a long time.
为什么
Why?
现在你还没有针对我客户的动作
As of right now, you have no action pending against my client.
但明早就有了
But as of tomorrow, I do,
因为明早起诉书就要提出了
'cause those indictments are coming down in the morning.